1. callTestCase(findTestCase("Common Test Cases/Navigate to Authentication Page"), null, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. openBrowser(G_SiteURL)
5. maximizeWindow()
9. click(findTestObject("Page_Home/lnk_SignIn"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
13. verifyMatch(getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Authentication/txa_title_Authentication Page")).toLowerCase(), "authentication", false, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Authentication/lnk_Forgot Your Password"))
9. verifyMatch(getText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Forgot Your Password/txa_title_Forgot Your Password")).toLowerCase(), "forgot your password?", false, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
13. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Forgot Your Password/btn_Retrieve Password"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
17. verifyMatch(getText(findTestObject("Page_Forgot Your Password/msg_Alert")).toLowerCase(), "there is 1 error
invalid email address.", false, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
21. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Forgot Your Password/txt_Email Address"), Email)
25. switch (com.example.WebUICustomKeywords.CheckInput(Email))
2. comment("Email was registered")
6. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_Forgot Your Password/btn_Retrieve Password"))
10. verifyMatch(getText(findTestObject("Page_Forgot Your Password/msg_Alert")).toLowerCase(), "a confirmation email has been sent to your address: " + RegisteredEmail, false, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
1. closeBrowser()