3. Call test case to navigate to 'Authentication' Page
3. Open Browser and Navigate to Home Page
9. Maximize Window
15. Click on 'Sign In' link in Main Menu
21. Verify navigation to 'Authentication' Page
9. Navigate to 'Forgot your password' Page
15. Verify was redirected to 'Forgot your password' Page
21. Click button 'Retrieve Password' with no data
27. Verify alert
33. Input an valid email which was not registered before
39. Click button 'Retrieve Password' with Email was not registered
45. Verify alert
51. Input an invalid email address
57. Click button 'Retrieve Password' with invalid email
63. Verify alert
69. Input an email was registered
75. Click button Retrieve Password with an email wasn't registered
81. Verify alert